Notre Dame: Alumni Association
Alumni Association
- Alumni Association: Graphics, 1990s-; GALM
  - Digital Images, c2003-; GALM
    - Football Game Day - Notre Dame vs. Stanford - Alumni Association Rev. William Corby Award Presentation to Lieutenant General Henry A. "Trey" Obering III, including with Chuck Lennon, Tim Dukeman, Air Force ROTC Color Guard; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [16 photos], 2008/1004; GALM
    - Photos submitted for the Alumni Association's "We Are ND" book, 2008; GALM
      - "We Are ND" Book - Anthony (Class of 1980) and Elizabeth (Goerner) Crisafi (Class of 1981) wedding photo. Photo donated by the Crisafis., c1990s; GALM-Crisafi-01.tif Story #46
      - "We Are ND" Book - Anthony (Class of 1980) and Elizabeth (Goerner) Crisafi (Class of 1981). Photo donated by the Crisafis., c1980; GALM-Crisafi-02.tif Story #46
      - "We Are ND" Book - Commencement - Sister Marie Malachy Griffin, OP, in cap and gown. Donated by Sister Marie Malachy Griffin, OP., 1989; GALM-Griffin-01.tif 141-2:
      - "We Are ND" Book - Commencement - Sister Marie Malachy Griffin, OP, at in cap and gown. Left to right: Margaret Lynch, Sister M. James Griffin OP, Sister Marie Malachy Griffin, and Shannon Crimmins. Children: Conor, Kelly, and Colin Crimmins. Donated by Sister Marie Malachy Griffin, OP., 1989; GALM-Griffin-02.tif 141-2:
      - "We Are ND" Book - Ted Drake watercolor of the Leprechaun. Scanned from the drawing in the Alumni Association Eck Visitors' Center. This image cannot be used without permission from the Notre Dame Licensing Department., c1964; GALM-Leprechaun.tif
      - "We Are ND" Book - Full page from a scrapbook. Football Game Scenes - Notre Dame vs. Iowa. Photos donated by Orlando Maione., 1953/1121; GALM-Maione-01.tif
      - "We Are ND" Book - Full page from a scrapbook. Football Game Scenes - Notre Dame vs. Iowa. Halftime Entertainment with Notre Dame's Marching Band, Irish Guard, Tim McCarthy, an American Indian from West Virginia. Photos donated by Orlando Maione., 1953/1121; GALM-Maione-02.tif
      - "We Are ND" Book - Notre Dame Law School Commencement - Graduate Mary P. Malone (BA 1983, BS 1983, JD 1993) with her parents Jim and Ronnie Malone. Donated by Mary P. Malone., 1993/05; GALM-Malone-01.tif GALM 144-4:
      - "We Are ND" Book - Student Bob Martina from Denver on campus with his bicycle. Donated by Bob Martina., c1942; GALM-Martina-01.tif GALM 278-3:
      - "We Are ND" Book - Main Building exterior. Donated by Bob Martina., 1942; GALM-Martina-02.tif GALM 278-3:
      - "We Are ND" Book - The hand on the statue of Mary on top of the Main Building Dome. Donated by Bob Martina., 1942; GALM-Martina-03.tif GALM 278-3:
      - "We Are ND" Book - Senior portrait of John McMahon. Donated by John McMahon., c1955; GALM-McMahon-01.tif GALM 006-4:
      - "We Are ND" Book - Kyle Meade (Class of 2000), as a child, receiving a Notre Dame Irish sweatshirt as a gift. Photo donated by Kyle Meade., c1980s; GALM-Meade-01.tif Story #280
      - "We Are ND" Book - Kyle Meade (Class of 2000), as a child, sitting in his bedroom, decorated in a Notre Dame theme. Photo donated by Kyle Meade., 1988/1026; GALM-Meade-02.tif Story #280
      - "We Are ND" Book - Football Game Day - Kyle Meade (Class of 2000), center as a child, sitting on the tailgate of a station wagon with two family members, c1990s; GALM-Meade-03.tif Story #280
      - "We Are ND" Book - Vetville Students Party at Lake Michigan with a football courtesy of Coach Frank Leahy. Kneeling (left to right): AG and John Murphy (Classes of 1944 and 1947); Jack Hupf (1944/1947); Rev. Theodore M. Hesburgh (1939); Joe Lane (1944/1949 JD); F.X. "Tim" Bradley (1939); unidentified. Standing: Bill Hooley (1944/1948); Mary Whitaker (Apartment 1C); Janet Hooley; Craig Whitaker (1949); and Loring Webber (1944/1947). Photo donated by John Murphy (Class of 1944 and 1947)., GALM-Murphy-01.tif
      - "We Are ND" Book - Brother Meinrad, CSC, Badin Hall's Bookstore Manager, and "Black John" Murphy. Brother Meinrad was sophomore prefect (rector; resident assistant) for Badin Hall in 1942 and junior prefect for Walsh Hall in 1943. He was the referee for the students' wet towel wars. Photo donated by John Murphy (Class of 1944 and 1947)., GALM-Murphy-02.tif
      - "We Are ND" Book - A group of senior students who were extras in the movie "Knute Rockne All American," posed on Main Quad, 1939-1940. Washington Hall is in the background. Seated (left to right): Joe Carlucci, Ed Delahanty, Bob Sanford, Tom Hosty, Herb Connelly, Lou Reilly, Joe Del Gaizo, Don Foskett, Neil Geary, Bill Schaller, Joe O'Connell, John "Red" Martin, CB McKenna, unidentified. Standing: Jim Hufnagel, Tom Duffy, unidentified, unidentified, Tom Lloyd, Ernie Timpani, John Henebry, Ken Collin, John Mack, unidentified, Chuck Magner, Tom O'Reilly, Ed Habecker, Ford, Pete Alonzi, unidentified, Bernie Crawford, Paul Morrison, Hal Barres. Photo donated by Bob Sanford (Class of 1940)., GALM-Sanford-01.tif Story #50
    - Alumni Association Thomas Dooley Award to Michael Brady, MD, Reception, including with Chuck Lennon, Darrell "Flash" Gordon; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [55 photos], 2009/0130; GALM
    - Football Game Day - Notre Dame vs. Washington State University - Distinguished Alumnus Award to Major General Frederick Roggero and Wounded Warrior Captain Wendy Sue Kosek, including with Chuck Lennon, Coach Charlie Weis, Irish Guard; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [122 photos], 2009/1031; GALM
    - Alumni Association Reunion - Rev. Edward Sorin Award to John J. McDonough presentation, including with Chuck Lennon, Rev. John I. Jenkins, Lou Nanni, Dolly Duffy; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [167 photos], 2009/0606; GALM
    - Winter Alumni Association Board of Directors Meeting - Rev. Anthony Lauck Award to Charles Kleibacker and Rev. Robert F. Griffin Award to Jerry Krammer Reception, including with Rev. Theodore M. Hesburgh, Lou Nanni, Dolly Duffy, Bob Franken [172 photos], 2009/0131; GALM
    - Alumni Association Board of Directors; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [2 photos], 2010/0909; GALM
    - Alumni Association Rev. William Corby Award to Captain Wendy Sue Kosek Reception, including with Tim Dukeman, Chuck Lennon, Michael Wong, Bob Franken; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [69 photos], 2010/0909; GALM
    - Football Game Day - Notre Dame vs. Michigan - Alumni Association Rev. William Corby Award presentation to Captain Wendy Sue Kosek at halftime; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [35 photos], 2010/0911; GALM
    - Alumni Association Dr. Tom Dooley Award to Victor DuKay Reception, including with Chuck Lennon, Michael Wong, Bob Franken; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [28 photos], 2010/0910; GALM
    - Alumni Senate Leadership Conference Dinner - Dr. Tom Dooley Award to Thomas Tauras, including with Chuck Lennon; photos by Eric Szajko, Lighthouse Imaging [416 photos], 2010/0414; GALM
    - Individual portraits of Alumni Association Board Members, including Christopher Putt; photos by Michael and Susan Bennett [271 photos], 2010/0414; GALM
    - Alumni Association Senate Leadership Conference Awards Luncheon, including with Chuck Lennon, Distinguished Graduate Student Rebecca J. McCumbers, Distinguished Undergraduate Student James Redden, and Mike Russo Character Award Winner Adrianna Garcia; photos by Michael and Susan Bennett [68 photos], 2010/0415; GALM
    - Alumni Associate Board of Directors Reception in the Notre Dame Stadium locker room, including with Michael Wong, Karen Putt, Chuck Lennon, Bates, Biggs, Brick, Colman, Connors, Delany, Dillenberger, Sullivan, Meeghan and Patrick Mousaw, Darrell "Flash" Gordon, Kerwin, Hediger, Hernandez, Valsaint, King, Larkin, LeeVan, Loosbrock, Lupo, McFarlane, Beth Ann McLane, Navarro, Read-Smith, Scarborough, Trevino-Berendzen, Patricia Trost, Tyler; photos by Brad Goff [165 photos], 2010/0129; GALM
    - Alumni Association Hesburgh Lecture, including with Karen Conway, Chuck Lennon; photos by Brad Goff [44 photos], 2010/0128; GALM
    - Alumni Association Rev. Anthony Lauck Award to Rev. Austin Collins Reception, including Karen Conway, Chuck Lennon; photos by Brad Goff [41 photos], 2010/0128; GALM
    - Alumni Association Board of Directors; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [4 photos], 2011/0901; GALM
    - Alumni Association Harvey G. Foster Award to Haley Scott DeMaria Reception, including with Alumni Director Dolly Duffy; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [4 photos], 2011/0901; GALM
    - Alumni Association Rev. William Corby Award to Lieutenant Commander Robert L. Miller Sr. Reception, including with Alumni Director Dolly Duffy; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [6 photos], 2011/0901; GALM
    - Alumni Association Rev. John J. Cavanaugh Award to Rev. David Garcia Reception, including with Alumni Director Dolly Duffy; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [34 photos], 2011/0902; GALM
    - Football Game Day - Notre Dame vs. University of South Florida (USF) - Alumni Association Harvey G. Foster Award presentation to Haley Scott DeMaria at halftime, including with Alumni Director Dolly Duffy; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [4 photos], 2011/0903; GALM
    - Alumni Association Senate Leadership Conference Rev. Robert F. Griffin Award to Brian Doyle Reception, including with Rev. David Tyson, Rev. Edward "Monk" Malloy, Christopher Putt, Michael Wong, Rev. Jim Gallagher, Dolly Duffy; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [56 photos], 2011/0413; GALM
    - Individual portraits of new Alumni Association Board Members and Administrative Assistant Patricia Trost; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [27 photos, including some duplicates], 2011/0413; GALM
    - Alumni Senate Leadership Conference - Club Awards Dinner at Club Naimoli in the Purcell Pavilion at the Joyce Athletic and Convocation Center (JACC), including Chuck Lennon, Michael Wong; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [53 photos], 2011/0414; GALM
    - Alumni Senate Leadership Conference Student Awards Luncheon in the Morris Inn, including with Beth Ann McLane, Michael Wong; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [42 photos], 2011/0414; GALM
    - Alumni Senate Leadership Conference Award Luncheon in the Morris Inn - James E. Armstrong Award to Michael J. Danch and Family Exemplar Award to Aileen and John Crowley, including with Michael Wong, Chuck Lennon; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [38 photos], 2011/0415; GALM
    - Alumni Senate Leadership Conference - Reception honoring former Alumni Association Director Chuck Lennon, including with Joan Lennon, Rev. Theodore M. Hesburgh, Rev. Edward "Monk" Malloy, Rev. John I. Jenkins, Lou Nanni, Michael Wong, Dolly Duffy, the Glee Club; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [430 photos, including some duplicate versions], 2011/0415; GALM
    - Alumni Senate Leadership Conference - Rev. Louis J. Putz Award to Neil K. Hitz Reception, including with Chuck Lennon, Dolly Duffy, Michael Wong; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [37 photos], 2011/0416; GALM
    - Alumni Senate Leadership Conference - "Partner with Mike McCoy" poster exhibit; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman, 2011/0416; GALM
    - Alumni Association Administrative Assistant Patricia Trost holding Zara Dukeman; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [2 photos], 2011/0416; GALM
  - Prints and Negatives, GALM